tigerwoodsfoundation.org 2017-03-30

# About: Privacy Policy | Tiger Woods Foundation

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY (THIS "PRIVACY POLICY") CAREFULLY BEFORE USING OUR WEBSITE OR ANY OTHER TIGER WOODS FOUNDATION PRODUCT OR SERVICE.

Tiger Woods Foundation in association with MLB Advanced Media, L.P. produces and publishes [www.TigerWoodsFoundation.org](http://www.tigerwoodsfoundation.org/), the Official Website of the Tiger Woods Foundation ( this or our "Website")This Privacy Policy is applicable to this Website and describes what information we collect, how we may use that information and the choices we offer for you to manage the information we collect related to your use of this Website.

**TABLE OF CONTENTS**

  1. Personal Information Collected Via This Website
  2. How We Use and Share Your Personal Information
  3. Other Information Collected And Shared Within This Website
  4. Other Circumstances When Your Data May Be Shared
  5. Managing Your Information
  6. Other Information

**1\. Personal Information Collected Via This Website** ****

**Information You Provide.** You may visit and enjoy many elements of our Website without disclosing any personal information about yourself. However, to make use of select, special or enhanced elements of this Website, you will need to share with us certain personal information so those elements may function properly. When you use certain enhanced elements within our Website (e.g., create a profile, register for newsletter list, or make a donation), the personal information we collect may include, but is not limited to:

  * Full name,
  * Email address,
  * Password,
  * Street address,
  * Telephone number(s),
  * Birth date,
  * Payment card information,
  * Location data,
  * Contacts (as stored in your wireless device),
  * Other personal data as detailed in this Privacy Policy and data that may be requested from and provided by you.

If we collect such information, in most instances, the applicable page(s) or location(s) within this Website will include statements regarding what information is required for the elements of this Website to function properly and functionality for you to submit the requested or required information. In addition to the list above, there may also be opportunities for you to grant permission for use of other of your information in a manner set forth on the applicable page(s) within this Website. 

**2\. How We Use and Share Your Personal Information** ****

If you submit personal information to us, or to any third party acting on our behalf, we may use and share your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy and as disclosed when you first submit your information. We will not sell, lease, publish or share your personal information with or to anyone else, except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may use and share your personal information as described in Section 1 above and we may:

  * Use your information to provide services you've requested or provide you with offers, promotions (e.g., a sweepstakes, fantasy game, subscription to goods or services, etc.) or content or add you to our postal mail list;
  * Share your information with certain third parties, including service providers, sponsors and promotional partners, so they may help us provide services, offers, promotions or content you've requested or otherwise in accordance with the applicable rules of a promotion or terms presented at the time you submit personal information, so the third party can administer the promotion, send you offers or content or add you to their postal mailing list;
  * Share your information upon notice posted on an applicable location of this Website where we collect your personal information for an economic transaction and notify you that we will be sharing such information with a third party; **or**
  * Use and share your information with permission from you.

**3\. Other Information Collected And Shared Within This Website** ****

  * _Our Cookies and Web Beacons_

We use and permit automatic methods such as cookies (small amounts of data which include a unique string of characters sent to your browser or application from a website's computers and stored on your computer's or device's hard drive), web beacons (technology used to track activity, also known as pixel tags) or similar technologies, alone or in combination with personally identifiable information you choose to provide us. Examples of the information we collect and analyze using such methods include, but is not limited to: personal information as authorized by you, the Internet protocol address used to connect your computer or device to the Internet; email address; login name and password; operating system type, version and computer or device platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locator clickstream to, on and from this Website, including date and time; and products you viewed or searched. We use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks and mouse-overs) and methods used to browse away from a page. We use and may allow certain third parties, such as those who provide services associated with this Website, to access these automatic data collection methods to enable you to use a "shopping cart" while using this Website, to store your preferences and to improve, deliver and customize this Websites' content and offerings.

  * _Third Party Cookies and Web Beacons; Network Advertisers_

We allow select third parties, such as those who deliver advertisements, content, social networking or provide other services associated with this Website, to set cookies, web beacons or similar technologies in certain locations within this Website or certain emails sent by us. Third party companies that manage and deliver advertisements to websites and applications such as ours are commonly referred to as "network advertisers." A permitted network advertiser may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to collect information about your interaction with this Website in order to tailor certain advertisements and content delivered within this Website and on other websites within such network advertiser's ad network. You may elect to opt out of targeted behavioral advertising from many major third party network advertisers by [clicking here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). If you would like to obtain more information about common industry practices of network advertisers or make choices about their use of your information or find additional opt-out tools operated by advertising industry associations encompassing even more network advertisers, please [click here](http://www.aboutads.info/).

  * _Social Networking_

When using this Website or when using certain third party social networking services (e.g., Facebook, Twitter, Google +) (each and collectively, a "Social Network"), you may have the option to connect your Website information and activity with your Social Network information and activity. If you authorize such a connection, you permit us to share or publish information about your activity on this Website, with that Social Network and its users, and to access certain of your Social Network information, as disclosed by you at the time you consent to the connection. Information we may share with a Social Network may include, but is not limited to: technical information about your Website activity, your Website comments or the videos you watch on this Website. Information we may access about you, with your consent, from a Social Network may include, but is not limited to, your basic Social Network information, your location data, your list of contacts, friends or followers, and certain of your activities on the Social Network. If you permit a connection between a Social Network and this Website, we (and that Social Network) may be able to identify you and to associate information received pursuant to the connection with information we already have about you. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policy and privacy control options of any Social Network with which you choose to share information or connect to this Website.

**4\. Other Circumstances When Your Data May Be Shared**

  * _Aggregated Demographic Information._

We may share aggregated demographic information with third parties. This information is not linked to personal information that can identify you or another individual person.

  * _Business Transfers._

As time passes, Tiger Woods Foundation and/or MLB Advanced Media, L.P. may be sold along with its assets, or other corporate transactions may occur. In such a case, our customer information may be one of the business assets we transfer.

  * _Disclosure for Legal Purposes._

We may be required to share your personal and non-personal information pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants or orders. If we are required to do so, we will, of course, obey the law. In addition, notwithstanding any term to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to use, disclose or share your personal and non-personal information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of Terms of Use of this Website or as required by law.

**5\. Managing Your Information**

You may choose and control what information you provide about yourself and certain information which is automatically collected via this Website. If you do not wish to provide certain information necessary for enhanced functionality or content on this Website, please do not use such functionality or content. If you have registered for an account through this Website, you may review and revise certain of your account information by [clicking here](http://www.mailing.tigerwoodsfoundation.org/landing/twf-signup) to log in, and then navigating the left-hand menu options. You may modify your subscriptions to our various promotional email communications and newsletters by accessing the "Profile" section within your Website account.

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows a user to accept or reject most cookies. Certain cookies that are set when some video products are accessed on our Website, called local shared objects or Flash cookies, may not be managed using the settings in your web browser. Information on managing, accepting and rejecting these cookies is available from Adobe on the [Adobe website](http://www.adobe.com/). If you set your browser or Adobe Flash options _not_ to accept cookies or local shared objects, you may not be able to take advantage of certain elements of this Website.

If you want to review or revise the personal information you provided during registration or in connection with a purchase or other activity while using this Website, or change the promotional email communications or newsletters you receive from us and/or our partners, you may click [here](http://www.mailing.tigerwoodsfoundation.org/landing/twf-signup) to log in, and then click on the applicable left-hand menu option. If you want to close your Website account and have us delete the personal information in it (except for information that we keep for record-keeping purposes), you should call TigerWoodsFoundation.org Customer Service at [twf@website.tigerwoods.com](mailto:twf@website.tigerwoods.com).

Remember that when you share information publicly online, it may be indexable by search engines or recorded by others, and any search engine index or record of your information may persist after you delete the information at the original source.

**6\. Other Information**

Our Website contains links to other Websites produced by MLB Advanced Media, L.P. and to Websites operated by unrelated third parties. In addition, if you click on an advertisement on this Website, you may be directed to a web page within this Website or to a third- party Website. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of third-party Websites. We encourage you to be aware of this when your leave this Website and to read the privacy policies of every Website that collects personally identifiable information from you. This Privacy Policy applies only to this Website.

  * _No Spyware or Adware._

We do not install any spyware or adware in connection with this Website, or distribute any commercial message, or authorize any third party to distribute any commercial message, by means of spyware or adware. "Spyware" or "adware" is any software which has been downloaded to or installed on an Internet user's computer or device, without the user's actual consent, and facilitates the distribution of any commercial message to the user. If you feel you may have spyware from another company installed on your machine, there are various anti-spyware/adware software applications available on the Internet to identify if this has occurred.

  * _Our Security Practices._

The account information associated with this Website is password protected for your privacy and security. You choose your password for any of our Services so the strength of that password is determined by you. We recommend that you choose a unique password and not share your password with anyone else. In certain areas, we use industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

  * _Links._

This Website contains links to other websites and products produced by MLB Advanced Media, L.P. and to websites and products operated by unrelated third parties. In addition, if you click on an advertisement within this Website, you may be directed to a web page within this Website or to a third party website or product. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites or products, and we encourage you to read the privacy policies of every website and product that collects personally identifiable information from you. This Privacy Policy applies only to this Website, unless you are notified otherwise upon accessing any third party website or product, in which case the terms and conditions set forth in such notification will apply.

  * _Your California Privacy Rights._

If you are a resident of California, pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, you may request information regarding our disclosure of your personal information to a third party for that party's direct marketing purposes. Any such disclosure made to a third party by us would be otherwise in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. To make such a request please send an email to [privacy@website.mlb.com](mailto:privacy@website.mlb.com) or write to us at: MLB Advanced Media, L.P., Privacy Administrator, 75 Ninth Avenue, New York, New York 10011.

  * _Special Rules For Children._

Because of federal law, we are not permitted to knowingly collect any personal information from a child under the age of thirteen without the consent of that child's parent or guardian. The statements in this Privacy Policy about our collection and use of personal information also apply to our treatment of personal information from children under the age of thirteen. Some elements of this Website (e.g., store) require the submission of a payment card number along with personal information in connection with a purchase; other elements of this Website (e.g., fantasy games) require the submission of personal information to access or use this Website. Except in certain cases where limited contact information may be collected and not retained, these elements of this Website are available to children under the age of thirteen. If a child who we know to be under the age of thirteen and for whom we have not received parental consent attempts to utilize a service on this Website which is not available to children, he/she will not be able to access it and may receive a message which relays that he/she is not eligible for such feature.

  * _Contact Us Regarding Privacy._

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at: [twf@website.tigerwoods.com](mailto:twf@website.tigerwoods.com).

  * _Notification of Changes._

If we make an important change to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notification and link on this Website's homepage so that you may review the updated policy.

**LAST UPDATED AND EFFECTIVE DATE: February 29, 2016**
